I have now seen two incredibly disturbing videos of black women clearly in the throes of labor.
So we're not talking about dilated three centimeters. We're talking about
10 centimeters dilated about to give birth. And the nurse is putting them through a triage process
as if they are not requiring emergency care. Okay. First, we know that that is absolutely
unacceptable. It is deeply disturbing. It is also representative of the United States
and the care that it has always put aside for black people. In addition, and I used to say this
all the time on my radio show, The Amanda Seale Show, before it was canceled by Radio 1, we are being
forced back into segregation. And you can either be proactive about that or reactive. Our doulas,
our midwives. And let me be clear, when I say our, I am not simply speaking about black people.
When I say our, I'm talking about people who care about life, people who care about the actual
existence of experiencing existence. We have to begin and continue, because some people have been
doing this, to form communities that serve each other without expectation of systems and institutions
that have never been here for us. This is also why we need to understand herbology. We need to
understand indigenous knowledge of that which has supported humans forever. And we need to understand
how to give birth and how to assist with birth. All of these things are a part of community, not just
food security, not just looking after each other's children once they are born. To those sisters,
you deserved better. And I'm so glad that you had people around you to pull you through
when these individuals showed their devilish nature.
Beats of Filfast in the dark of early morn.